Alright, in this video, I'm going to look at the paper, Generative Agents, Interactive Simulcra of Humanity.
好的，在这个视频中，我将看看论文，生成代理，人类的交互式模拟。
So what I'm going to do is go through the paper.
所以我要做的是浏览论文。
I'm also going to reproduce some of this in GPT-4.
我还将在 GPT-4 中重现其中的一些内容。
And we're going to have a look at how you would do these Generative Agents, etc.
我们将看看您将如何做这些生成代理等。
Using some of the ideas from the paper if you wanted to do it yourself.
如果您想自己做，请使用论文中的一些想法。
So this paper is all about creating autonomous agents that can at least have the illusion of thinking.
因此，这篇论文是关于创建至少可以具有思维错觉的自主代理。
So actually Simulcra is creating like likenesses or a reflection, a representation of human behavior in here.
所以实际上Simulcra正在创造类似的相似或反射，在这里表现人类行为。
And that's what they're trying to create in here.
这就是他们试图在这里创造的东西。
And they do it with a very nice little game.
他们用一个非常好的小游戏来做到这一点。
So we'll have a look at the game as well.
所以我们也会看看游戏。
They've put up a demo online where you can actually watch what's going on,
他们在网上放了一个演示，你可以实际观看正在发生的事情，
see the different agents, and there's 25 of these agents going at a time.
查看不同的代理，一次有 25 个这样的代理。
And we can also see what they're doing.
我们也可以看到他们在做什么。
So we can see a lot of them are asleep.
所以我们可以看到他们中的很多人都睡着了。
If we click on one of them, it'll take us to where they are.
如果我们点击其中一个，它会把我们带到他们所在的地方。
And we can actually watch what they're doing.
我们实际上可以观察他们在做什么。
We can also see their current action here and the details about them.
我们还可以看到他们当前的行动 这里 以及有关他们的详细信息。
This is very cool because it's doing 25 different agents at a time.
这非常酷，因为它一次做25个不同的代理。
But really it's come up with a system for doing many agents.
但实际上，它提出了一个可以做许多代理的系统。
So I don't see why this couldn't be scaled up to even a lot more agents.
所以我不明白为什么这不能扩展到更多的代理。
The only limitations are the pinging the large language model, etc.
唯一的限制是 ping 大型语言模型等。
So let's jump in and have a look at what this is and how it's doing.
因此，让我们跳进去看看这是什么以及它是如何做的。
I'll point out that so these are the authors up here.
我要指出的是，这些是这里的作者。
Percy Leung is probably the supervisor, I'm guessing.
Percy Leung可能是主管，我猜。
On this, he was also on the Alpaca paper and many other things that have come out of Stanford.
在这一点上，他还在羊驼纸和斯坦福大学的许多其他东西上。
Some of Google research people also on this paper.
一些谷歌研究人员也对这篇论文感兴趣。
So they basically are setting out to create a way to make a simulation of human behavior
因此，他们基本上正在着手创建一种模拟人类行为的方法。
and interactivity between humans and objects and humans and other humans here.
以及人类与物体以及人类与其他人之间的互动性。
To do that, they've created this sort of game world.
为了做到这一点，他们创造了这种游戏世界。
And while the game world is quite nice for us to be able to see it, it's not the coolest thing.
虽然游戏世界对我们来说非常好，但这并不是最酷的事情。
By far, how they've actually put it all together is really good.
到目前为止，他们实际上如何将它们放在一起真的很好。
So they refer to this as the interactive sandbox environment that they've got going on here.
所以他们把这个称为他们在这里进行的交互式沙盒环境。
So what they're basically doing is getting these generative agents and creating an architecture
所以他们基本上要做的是获得这些生成代理并创建一个架构。
that allows them to use large language models to store records of memory, experience,
这允许他们使用大型语言模型来存储记忆、经验、
and then to synthesize from those actions and planning that they can take for actions in the future.
然后从这些行动和计划中综合起来，他们可以在未来采取行动。
And it turns out that this works really well and brings out a lot of really interesting traits
事实证明，这非常有效，并带出了很多非常有趣的特征
both in what they do and also how it's done.
无论是他们做什么还是怎么做。
So one of the examples is that one of the agents comes up with the idea of a Valentine's Day party
所以一个例子是，其中一位经纪人提出了情人节派对的想法。
and starts to spread that through conversation to other agents.
并开始通过对话将其传播给其他代理。
And then the idea of that party gets spread right across the simulation
然后那个派对的想法在整个模拟中传播开来。
and people actually end up showing up for this party that they've created themselves.
人们最终会出现在他们自己创建的这个派对上。
So you go through a quite in-depth in the paper.
所以你在论文中进行了相当深入的介绍。
I'm not going to go through everything in the paper,
我不会在论文中浏览所有内容，
but we're going to look at some of the key things that are going on here.
但是我们将看看这里正在发生的一些关键事情。
The idea here is that to enable these generative agents, they make this agent architecture.
这里的想法是，为了启用这些生成代理，他们制作了这种代理体系结构。
And this architecture basically stores memories, synthesizes things,
而这个架构基本上是存储记忆，合成东西，
and applies these relevant memories to generate believable behavior using a large language model.
并应用这些相关记忆，使用大型语言模型生成可信的行为。
They talk about their architecture comprising of three parts,
他们谈论他们的架构由三个部分组成，
the memory stream, which we'll look at, the long-term memory module, and the natural language parts,
记忆流，我们将看到，长期记忆模块和自然语言部分，
which we'll also look at, and we'll try to recreate in GPT-4, just through playing around with this as well.
我们也将研究它，我们将尝试在 GPT-4 中重新创建，只是通过玩这个。
They've also got a bunch of retrieval models.
他们还有一堆检索模型。
And then that's all in the first part.
然后这就是第一部分的全部内容。
Then they've got this really interesting idea of reflection.
然后他们有了这个非常有趣的反思想法。
So if you're a fan of Westworld, one of the whole themes in Westworld
所以如果你是西部世界的粉丝，这是西部世界的全部主题之一
was this idea of these agents reflecting back on their own memories and their own experiences.
是这些特工反思自己的记忆和自己的经历的想法。
And that's kind of what this is doing, maybe not in the same way as Westworld.
这就是它正在做的事情，也许与《西部世界》的方式不同。
But they've got this reflection idea, which synthesizes memories into higher-level inferences over time.
但他们有这个反思的想法，随着时间的推移，它将记忆合成成更高层次的推理。
And you could argue that's something that humans actually do.
你可以说这是人类实际做的事情。
We take in what we see day to day, we then kind of chunk it together,
我们吸收我们每天看到的东西，然后我们把它分成几块，
and we basically get it to a point where if I ask you to describe a day from last week,
我们基本上把它弄到一个地步，如果我让你描述上周的一天，
you're probably not going to remember all the details, but you'll remember that,
你可能不会记住所有的细节，但你会记住，
"Oh, yeah, I got in my car, I drove to this place, I met this person," those sorts of things.
“哦，是的，我上了车，我开车去了这个地方，我遇到了这个人，”诸如此类的事情。
So that's sort of the higher-level stuff.
所以这是更高层次的东西。
And the third thing that they're really aiming at is this planning,
他们真正瞄准的第三件事是这个计划，
which the idea of here is to basically take some of these conclusions that they've come up with
这里的想法基本上是采取他们提出的一些结论
and plan out actions that they can take with this.
并计划他们可以采取的行动。
Again, the generative agents is what you're seeing in the game.
同样，生成代理就是你在游戏中看到的。
For me, by far the more interesting part is actually the architecture that they've come up with to do this.
对我来说，到目前为止，更有趣的部分实际上是他们想出的架构。
They also go into some evaluation stuff, which I won't go into the video to how they evaluate it.
他们还进入了一些评估内容，我不会进入视频中他们如何评估它。
So they talk a little bit about different forms of believable proxies for human behavior,
所以他们谈论了人类行为的不同形式的可信代理，
what sort of come before for this kind of thing.
这种事情以前是什么样的。
And people have tried some ideas like this using RL,
人们已经使用RL尝试了一些这样的想法，
and they point out Alpha Star for Starcraft, the OpenAI5 for Dota,
他们指出星际争霸的Alpha Star，Dota的OpenAI5，
but they point out that those things are much more adversarial,
但他们指出，这些事情更具对抗性，
where you're trying to kill the opponent playing this game or something like that.
你试图杀死玩这个游戏或类似游戏的对手的地方。
Whereas here, they're looking much more for collaborative sort of things
而在这里，他们正在寻找更多的协作性的东西。
and more natural human behavior coming out of this.
以及由此产生的更自然的人类行为。
Another example of where people have done something like this in the past
另一个例子是人们过去做过这样的事情
was came out of Salesforce, where they actually tried to get an AI with RL
来自Salesforce，他们实际上试图通过RL获得AI。
to manage a simulated economy, which was also very interesting.
管理模拟经济，这也非常有趣。
And I do wonder if the next step for some of this is to start going in that direction
我确实想知道其中一些的下一步是否是开始朝着这个方向发展。
with the framework that these people have created.
与这些人创建的框架。
So you can see that this is their mock world.
所以你可以看到这是他们的模拟世界。
It's got a bunch of things like a park.
它有一堆东西，比如一个公园。
It's got places that people can go to in their houses.
它有人们可以在他们的房子里去的地方。
It's got different parts in the house so people can move around.
房子里有不同的部分，所以人们可以四处走动。
The generative agents can move around, can interact in these locations.
生成代理可以四处移动，可以在这些位置相互作用。
All right, so you can see first off, they talk about creating this idea of creating the agent.
好的，所以你可以看到首先，他们谈论创建这个创建代理的想法。
So they give an example here of a prompt to create an agent.
因此，他们在这里给出了一个提示创建代理的示例。
And this is sort of key to a lot of this is that what they will do is create the agents
这是很多关键，他们将要做的是创建代理。
and then they have like a time step in the game.
然后他们在游戏中有一个时间步。
So at every increment of time in the game, they ask each agent,
因此，在游戏中的每一个增量时间，他们都会问每个代理，
what are you doing, both what are you thinking and what action are you taking?
你在做什么，你在想什么，你在做什么行动？
And if they're in a conversation, what's the conversation, that kind of thing.
如果他们在对话，对话是什么，诸如此类。
So just to sort of show you an example of this, let's look at GPT-4,
所以为了向你展示一个例子，让我们看看 GPT-4，
where I've done the same kind of thing that we can look at here.
我做了同样的事情，我们可以在这里看到。
So we basically got your AI behind an NPC game character called David Bourne.
所以我们基本上让你的人工智能支持一个叫做大卫伯恩的NPC游戏角色。
Now, this prompt I've just put in there, I'm sure their prompts are probably much nicer.
现在，我刚刚放在那里的这个提示，我相信他们的提示可能更好。
And unfortunately, I don't think they've published all their prompts.
不幸的是，我认为他们没有发布所有的提示。
But then we can take an example description like what they have done.
但是，我们可以举一个示例描述，例如他们所做的。
And so here I've created this character.
所以在这里，我创造了这个角色。
I've used some of their description from some of the other people in there.
我使用了他们从其他一些人那里得到的一些描述。
But I've met a new character, right?
但是我遇到了一个新角色，对吧？
David Bourne is a restaurateur at the Jason Sushi restaurant on Brunswick Street, Fitzroy.
大卫·伯恩（David Bourne）是菲茨罗伊（Fitzroy）不伦瑞克街（Brunswick Street）杰森寿司餐厅（Jason Sushi restaurant）的餐馆老板。
And he's always looking to make the process of running his business easier for his customers.
他一直在寻求让客户更容易经营业务的过程。
So we can see a little bit about him.
所以我们可以看到一些关于他的信息。
He's married.
他结婚了。
We've got what his wife does.
我们有他妻子的所作所为。
We've got his his child here, what they're studying.
我们把他的孩子带到了这里，他们正在学习什么。
And we can see also his relationships with other people in there.
我们也可以看到他与其他人的关系。
So then what I basically have done is set this up so that each time step I enter the command, new time step.
因此，我基本上所做的就是设置它，以便每个时间步长我都输入命令，新的时间步长。
I want you to list the time of day and the action that David Bourne is taking in this conversation.
我希望你列出一天中的时间和大卫·伯恩在这次谈话中采取的行动。
And then I give it some examples, new time step six a.m. David is asleep, new time step.
然后我举一些例子，新的时间步长六点。大卫睡着了，新的时间步。
And then sure enough, it can generate, OK, 7.30 David is having breakfast with his family, new time step.
然后果然，它可以产生，好吧，7.30大卫正在和他的家人一起吃早餐，新的时间步长。
Now, in the game, I'm sure they're probably specifying actually when these new time steps, you know,
现在，在游戏中，我敢肯定他们可能正在指定这些新的时间步长，你知道，
if it's like every 10 minutes, every five minutes, that kind of thing.
如果像每10分钟，每5分钟，那种事情。
You can see the large language model is pretty good at sort of working out that, OK, at 7.30 a.m.
你可以看到大型语言模型非常擅长解决这个问题，好吧，早上7点30分。
You know, he's doing this at 9 a.m. David is opening Jason Sushi restaurant and preparing for the day's customers.
你知道，他是在早上9点做的。大卫正在开杰森寿司餐厅，为当天的顾客做准备。
OK, and then I basically say if he's in a conversation, show us the conversation.
好的，然后我基本上说如果他在谈话中，给我们看谈话。
So 11.30 he's taking a lunch order from his neighbor.
所以11点30分，他从邻居那里点了午餐。
And we can see that this is the conversation that occurred that, hi, David, I'd like to have some salmon.
我们可以看到，这是发生的对话，嗨，大卫，我想吃一些鲑鱼。
So she please, of course, and get a sense of what's going on here.
所以她当然会很高兴，并了解这里发生了什么。
And we can see there's other conversations going on.
我们可以看到还有其他对话正在进行中。
We can actually then ask it to generate a whole bunch of time steps here.
然后，我们实际上可以要求它在这里生成一大堆时间步长。
I've asked it to generate 10 between 3 p.m. and 10 p.m.
我要求它在下午 3 点到 10 点之间生成 10 个。
And you can see, sure enough, it gives these in a nice order and they make sense for the character that we've described that is David is the restaurateur.
你可以看到，果然，它以很好的顺序给出了这些，它们对于我们描述的角色是有意义的，大卫是餐馆老板。
And so that's kind of what they're doing here.
这就是他们在这里所做的。
Once they create these characters, is they're creating this idea of running it through in a time stamp.
一旦他们创建了这些角色，他们就是在创建在时间戳中运行它的想法。
And actually, later on, you see when they get to or jump around a bit, you'll see they're creating this sort of this is going into the eventually going to go into the memory stream of where we can see.
实际上，稍后，你会看到当他们到达或跳来跳去时，你会看到他们正在创造这种东西，最终会进入我们可以看到的内存流。
Okay, a timestamp of what the character is doing at the various time, et cetera.
好的，角色在不同时间所做的事情的时间戳，等等。
So in the paper, they do talk about that you can actually go in as a character yourself and interact with people.
所以在论文中，他们确实谈到了你实际上可以自己作为一个角色进入并与人互动。
And that will then change how they interact as well.
这也将改变他们的互动方式。
Because just as I showed you making the David Bourne, you would have one of these for each of the agents.
因为就像我展示你制作大卫·伯恩一样，你会为每个代理商提供一个这样的。
And each time they interact, this is where the memory comes in.
每次他们互动时，这就是记忆的来源。
So each of them has a memory of what they've done.
所以他们每个人都对自己所做的事情有记忆。
And they can go through, they can update that they can use that to plan for the next thing.
他们可以经历，他们可以更新，他们可以用它来计划下一件事。
So this example sort of day in the life gives them some of the key things that we were talking about with the time steps and stuff like that.
所以这个生命中的例子给了他们一些关键的事情，我们正在谈论的时间步长和类似的东西。
They point out that you start to see these social behaviors.
他们指出，你开始看到这些社会行为。
And for me, what's the really interesting part, though, is this kind of memory system.
对我来说，真正有趣的部分是这种记忆系统。
So let me look at the diagram and I'll go through it and explain what's going on.
所以让我看一下这张图，我会通过它并解释发生了什么。
So each character perceives something in the world.
所以每个角色都感知到世界上的一些东西。
So as we saw this get the GPT-4 explaining what David was doing, that's like him perceiving it.
所以当我们看到GPT-4解释大卫在做什么时，就像他感知到的那样。
That gets put into the memory stream.
这被放入内存流中。
And the memory stream will look something like this, where you've got time stamps with things that the character actually saw.
记忆流看起来像这样，你有时间戳，上面有角色实际看到的东西。
It's then got to basically work out how to use these memories and how to take actions.
然后，它基本上必须弄清楚如何使用这些记忆以及如何采取行动。
So to do that, it's got a few different things.
所以要做到这一点，它有一些不同的东西。
So it's got a way of retrieving memories and we'll look at the user's waiting system to do this.
所以它有一种检索记忆的方法，我们将看看用户的等待系统来做到这一点。
And then once it's retrieved, those memories, it either makes a plan and if it makes a plan,
然后一旦它被检索到，那些记忆，它要么制定一个计划，如果它制定一个计划，
that plan gets put back into a sort of memory of its own and or reflects on it.
这个计划被放回自己的记忆中，或者反思它。
So the whole idea of the reflection is very cool in that it can take a whole.
所以反射的整个想法非常酷，因为它可以采取一个整体。
You can sort of think about the reflection as being like a summarization.
你可以把反思想象成一个总结。
So it can take a conversation that David has had with someone talking about something for work.
因此，大卫可以与某人谈论工作方面的对话。
And then it can summarize the key parts of that that David needs to remember.
然后它可以总结大卫需要记住的关键部分。
And that will then go back into a sort of memory system there.
然后这将回到那里的某种内存系统中。
And these retrieved memories.
而这些找回的记忆。
So this is sort of a loop going around loops going around here.
所以这是一个循环，绕着这里循环。
These retrieved memories are then used with the plan to actually decide what actions to take.
然后，这些检索到的记忆与计划一起使用，以实际决定要采取什么行动。
Once it's got those relevant memories, once it's retrieved, those actions,
一旦它有了那些相关的记忆，一旦它被检索到，那些动作，
it determines the action and it takes the next step on this.
它确定操作并为此采取下一步措施。
So they go in in quite in depth about how they do the memory retrieval for this.
因此，他们非常深入地介绍了如何为此进行内存检索。
One of the cool things that they mentioned in here is this whole sort of waiting system
他们在这里提到的一件很酷的事情是整个等待系统
of like, how do you actually remember, you know, how do you actually determine what to focus on
比如，你如何真正记住，你知道，你如何真正确定要关注什么
and what's important kind of thing.
什么是重要的事情。
So you don't want to remember everything because that's just going to clutter it up.
所以你不想记住所有东西，因为这只会把它弄得乱七八糟。
And also the context span of the large language model is going to be too small
而且大型语言模型的上下文跨度也太小了
for you to put everything in to that context span.
以便您将所有内容都放入该上下文跨度中。
So they use basically a waiting system for doing this.
所以他们基本上使用一个等待系统来做到这一点。
And this brings up a whole interesting sort of thing as well.
这也带来了一件非常有趣的事情。
So they wait basically on recency.
所以他们基本上等待新近。
So obviously things that are more recent, you're going to remember more.
所以很明显，最近的事情，你会记住更多。
So they use that.
所以他们使用它。
And then that decays over time.
然后随着时间的推移而衰减。
So further the time steps are you away from that happening, the memory of that will be less.
所以你离那件事发生的时间步越远，对那件事的记忆就会更少。
They do the importance of something.
他们做某事的重要性。
So if something is important, then you're more likely to remember it.
因此，如果某件事很重要，那么你更有可能记住它。
Also the relevance is something that's going to determine you being able to remember something.
此外，相关性将决定你能够记住一些东西。
If it's a relevant topic to you, you're more likely to do this.
如果这是一个与你相关的话题，你更有可能这样做。
So you can see that these are the numbers that they're getting.
所以你可以看到这些是他们得到的数字。
The importance one is really interesting one because how do you decide what's important?
重要性一个非常有趣，因为你如何决定什么是重要的？
So they actually give you a prompt.
所以他们实际上给了你一个提示。
I've taken this and we've put this into GPT for we can play around with this.
我已经接受了这个，我们已经把它放到 GPT 中，因为我们可以玩这个。
So you can see this is the prompt on a scale of one to 10 where one is purely mundane.
所以你可以看到这是 1 到 10 的提示，其中 1 个是纯粹平凡的。
And 10 is extremely poignant rate the poignancy of the following piece of David's memory.
10是大卫接下来一段记忆的辛酸。
So the memory here would be ordering cleaning supplies for his restaurant
所以这里的记忆是为他的餐厅订购清洁用品
from the supermarket.
从超市。
That's going to get a rating of two.
这将得到两个评级。
And then I say, okay, applying for a loan from the bank for a restaurant expansion.
然后我说，好吧，向银行申请贷款，用于餐厅扩张。
Now this is something you would expect that would be much more important.
现在，这是您所期望的更重要的事情。
Sure enough, it gets a rating of seven.
果然，它得到了七分的评分。
Then I was interested to test that with things like that are more personal.
然后我有兴趣用这样更个人化的东西来测试它。
So we can kind of elicit David's values in some ways here that David's son getting in trouble
因此，我们可以在这里以某种方式引出大卫的价值观，大卫的儿子陷入困境
at school and David having to go to a parent teacher meeting next Tuesday.
在学校，大卫不得不去参加下周二的家长会。
Well, that's a six for him.
嗯，这对他来说是六分。
It's not as important as his expansion, but it's obviously a lot more important than
这不像他的扩张那么重要，但显然比他重要得多
him ordering the cleaning supplies.
他订购了清洁用品。
So each of these is just a sort of simple example.
所以每一个都只是一个简单的例子。
And this could be informed more by the character of David that we set up and we set up in his
这可以通过我们建立的大卫的性格来更多地告知他，我们在他身上设置的。
values in the prompt as well.
提示中的值。
And they may be doing something like that.
他们可能正在做类似的事情。
The idea once they've got this though, they're able to then sort of work out, okay,
不过，一旦他们有了这个想法，他们就能够解决，好吧，
what do you actually pay attention to in these?
在这些方面，你到底在注意什么？
And then from these memories, what gets passed to a language model to use for planning
然后从这些记忆中，将什么传递给语言模型以用于规划
or to use for planning and taking action or for doing reflections.
或用于计划和采取行动或进行反思。
This is where the reflections come in.
这就是反射的用武之地。
So generic evasions were equipped with only raw observations,
所以通用逃避只配备了原始观察，
struggle to generalize or make inferences.
努力概括或推断。
So this makes a lot of sense, right?
所以这很有意义，对吧？
If you think about it, that when you look at something only at a surface level,
如果你仔细想想，当你只在表面层面上看某事时，
humans don't really do that.
人类并没有真正这样做。
We tend to think things through and think how do they relate to other things in our life?
我们倾向于仔细思考问题，并思考它们与我们生活中的其他事物有何关系？
How, you know, what information was more important, that kind of thing.
你知道，什么信息更重要，诸如此类。
And this is where the reflection comes in.
这就是反射的用武之地。
So it can take things like conversations and actions and stuff like that.
所以它可以采取诸如对话和行动之类的事情。
And it can reflect on the higher level, more abstract thoughts from this.
它可以从中反映更高层次、更抽象的想法。
This is where they basically generate more thoughts doing this.
这就是他们基本上产生更多想法的地方。
And this is done through, they talk about here using a prompt where given only the information
这是通过完成的，他们在这里使用提示来谈论，其中仅提供信息
above, what are the three most salient high level questions we can answer about the subjects
以上，我们可以回答的关于这些主题的三个最突出的高级问题是什么
in the statements.
在声明中。
And they give some examples of talking to people, talking to this class smaller.
他们举了一些与人交谈的例子，与这个班级交谈。
And he's obviously perhaps in the conversation talking at a very low level, you know,
他显然可能在谈话中说话的水平很低，你知道，
about his research project and stuff like that.
关于他的研究项目和类似的东西。
The high level stuff is that he's writing a research paper.
高层次的东西是他正在写一篇研究论文。
He enjoys reading a book.
他喜欢看书。
He's conversing with these people, right?
他在和这些人交谈，对吧？
There's different things that are, you know, much more high level.
你知道，有不同的东西是更高水平的。
And they're kind of like the summarizations of the key things that we would pass into the
它们有点像我们将传递到关键事物的摘要
language model for doing the planning and doing the action steps that are in here.
用于执行此处的规划和操作步骤的语言模型。
Finally, coming to the planning and reacting.
最后，来到计划和反应。
Again, this is done through having a sequence, you know, they generate a sequence of future
同样，这是通过有一个序列来完成的，你知道，他们生成了一个未来的序列。
actions for the agent.
代理的操作。
And they try to, you know, the goal is to keep the agent's behavior consistent over time.
他们试图，你知道，目标是随着时间的推移保持代理的行为一致。
A plan includes a location, a starting time, a duration.
计划包括位置、开始时间、持续时间。
So that could be one of the characters going to the park and painting for four hours.
所以这可能是其中一个角色去公园画画四个小时。
So you've got the location, you've got what the actual action is doing, a starting time,
所以你有位置，你有实际行动正在做什么，一个开始时间，
duration in there.
持续时间在那里。
So they mentioned that like reflections, plans are stored in the memory stream and are
所以他们提到，像反射一样，计划存储在内存流中，并且
included in the retrieval process.
包含在检索过程中。
This allows the agent to consider observations, reflections and plans all together when deciding
这允许代理在决定时一起考虑观察、反思和计划
on how to behave.
关于如何表现。
So agents might change their plans midstream as well.
因此，代理商也可能在中游改变他们的计划。
So as they're doing these reflection things, as they're doing the planning, they're using
因此，当他们做这些反思的事情时，当他们做计划时，他们正在使用
this memory and they're sort of putting it in there just through generating it.
这个记忆，他们只是通过生成它把它放在那里。
You can see in here, they've given some examples based on this, what would actually be some of
你可以在这里看到，他们基于这个给出了一些例子，实际上会是一些
the plans.
计划。
And we can see that, okay, the plan might be to wake up, complete morning routine, go to
我们可以看到，好吧，计划可能是醒来，完成早晨的例行公事，去
college.
大学。
So this is for the student, you know, work on the particular projects from this time to
所以这是给学生的，你知道，从这个时候到特定的项目工作。
this time.
这一次。
It gives you a nice plan for this.
它为您提供了一个不错的计划。
And then that would be fed in with what we looked up earlier on to generate the next
然后，这将与我们之前查找的内容一起输入以生成下一个
time steps.
时间步长。
So the next time steps might change if they bump into someone.
因此，如果他们撞到某人，下一次步骤可能会改变。
But if they're just by themselves, they're probably going to stick to their plan over
但如果他们只是一个人，他们可能会坚持他们的计划。
time.
时间。
And you can see this, they talk about, you know, reacting and updating to plans.
你可以看到这一点，他们谈论，你知道，对计划做出反应和更新。
They operate in an action loop.
它们在动作循环中运行。
So one of the big things is to understand this sort of game loop that's going on.
因此，最重要的事情之一是了解正在发生的这种游戏循环。
That at each point, like a new time is set, and all the characters or all the agents go
在每个点上，就像设定了一个新的时间，所有的角色或所有的代理人都去了
through and run their evaluation and their planning and looking at their action and return
通过并运行他们的评估和计划，并查看他们的行动和回报
that that actually is getting stored in kind of like a graph or a tree structure that's
它实际上被存储在一种图形或树结构中，就像图形或树结构一样
used to in Jason to actually plot all this out.
曾经在杰森身上实际策划了这一切。
So when we're looking at this, if I come down here, we want to find, let's say we find this
所以当我们看到这个时，如果我来到这里，我们想找到，假设我们找到了这个。
character running around.
角色跑来跑去。
This is actually all just using a game engine called phaser that they're using to do this.
这实际上只是使用他们用来做到这一点的称为相位器的游戏引擎。
And my guess is that they've gone through, they may have made it from scratch, or they've
我的猜测是，他们已经经历了，他们可能是从头开始的，或者他们已经
they may have taken one of the tutorials and edited it.
他们可能已经接受了其中一个教程并对其进行了编辑。
You can see there are some examples of tutorials in here of how to build something a little
您可以在此处看到一些教程示例，说明如何构建一些东西
bit sort of like this.
有点像这样。
And using this, this is just plot, this is basically just rendering out from Jason.
而利用这个，这只是剧情，这基本上只是杰森的渲染。
So they do talk about in here that the goal of what they're doing is that this environment is
所以他们确实在这里谈论他们正在做的事情的目标是这个环境是
built with phaser that they're using Jason to actually store this and the sandbox it.
使用相位器构建，他们正在使用Jason来实际存储它和沙盒。
And then they kind of flatten out the Jason for feeding it into large language models.
然后他们把Jason弄扁了，把它输入到大型语言模型中。
So if there are certain things that you know they need from the Jason, they've obviously got some
因此，如果你知道他们需要从杰森那里得到某些东西，他们显然会得到一些
ways of deciding what they need and then taking those things and flattening them out.
决定他们需要什么，然后把这些东西弄平的方法。
There's a lot of engineering to this, not just AI stuff.
这有很多工程，而不仅仅是人工智能的东西。
There's a lot of really interesting sort of engineering going on in here.
这里有很多非常有趣的工程。
And yeah, they talk about how they put all this together.
是的，他们谈论他们如何将所有这些放在一起。
It is interesting to look at the prompts that they use.
看看他们使用的提示很有趣。
So one of the things I haven't covered is the dialogue.
所以我没有涉及的一件事是对话。
So they've got a whole sort of dialogue system of where they're basically just sort of kicking
所以他们有一个完整的对话系统，他们基本上只是踢球。
it off with a prompt and seeing, okay, what do they get back from the dialogue.
它通过提示结束，看看，好吧，他们从对话中得到了什么。
Those dialogues are fed into the memory of each of the agents that was involved in that
这些对话被输入到参与其中的每个代理人的记忆中
dialogue. That's where you get things like the Valentine's Day party is a dialogue of where one
对话。这就是你得到的东西的地方，比如情人节派对是一个人的对话
agent says to another one, hey, there's this party, it's on at this time.
经纪人对另一个人说，嘿，有这个派对，现在开始了。
And then that goes into the person who's listening's memory.
然后进入正在倾听的人的记忆。
And then they're able to use that to tell another agent.
然后他们能够用它来告诉另一个代理。
That's how it actually happens as we're going through this.
这就是我们正在经历这件事时实际发生的方式。
Anyway, unconscious, I've gone very long on this video.
无论如何，无意识的，我已经在这个视频上呆了很长时间。
I have a read of the paper.
我读过这篇论文。
Just try coming and try some of the ideas out in something like chat.
试着来试试聊天之类的想法。
She they actually use chat GPT, not GPT for for doing this.
她实际上使用聊天 GPT，而不是 GPT 来执行此操作。
And you can see that with just a little bit of playing with GPT for I was able to get this
你可以看到，只要玩一点点 GPT，我就能得到这个
generating similar kinds of things.
生成类似的东西。
So it does show that this is something that you could go through the paper and reproduce
所以它确实表明这是你可以通过论文并复制的东西
if you want to.
如果你愿意。
It's fun to just come back and look at the game itself and see what's going on, what they're doing.
回来看看游戏本身，看看发生了什么，他们在做什么，这很有趣。
We can see what's this person doing.
我们可以看到这个人在做什么。
If we look down here, we can see, okay, this is where they are.
如果我们往下看，我们可以看到，好吧，这就是他们所在的地方。
This is the conversation that they've got going on.
这是他们正在进行的对话。
And we can see they're changing over time.
我们可以看到它们随着时间的推移而变化。
Right.
右。
So if I pause it, we can stop it and look at it.
因此，如果我暂停它，我们可以停止它并查看它。
But we can see that if we follow one of these characters, we can see what's going on with them
但是我们可以看到，如果我们跟随其中一个角色，我们可以看到他们发生了什么。
over time.
随着时间的推移。
And this is just being rendered from the Jason, right, that we're looking at.
这只是从杰森那里渲染出来的，对，我们正在看的。
This is obviously, you know, probably not playing out in real time.
你知道，这显然不是实时播放的。
It's been created first with the language models.
它是首先使用语言模型创建的。
I imagine that all the calls to the different language models might take a little bit of time.
我想对不同语言模型的所有调用可能需要一点时间。
But once they've got this, they can then render out a whole day or something quite easily.
但是一旦他们有了这个，他们就可以很容易地渲染一整天或其他东西。
All right.
好吧。
So that was the paper, generative agents, interactive simulacra of human behavior.
这就是论文，生成代理，人类行为的交互式模拟。
Very cool paper, I think, some really interesting ideas.
非常酷的论文，我认为，一些非常有趣的想法。
You're definitely going to see this kind of thing happen and coming to sort of non-player
你肯定会看到这种事情发生，并且会变成非玩家。
characters in games.
游戏中的角色。
Also, a lot of uses for simulation and interactive role play with humans.
此外，模拟和与人类互动角色扮演的很多用途。
So allowing humans to try out different things before they actually do it in the real world
因此，允许人类在现实世界中实际尝试之前尝试不同的事情
is a really good use for this kind of technology.
是这种技术的一个很好的用途。
As always, if you have any questions, please put them in the comments below.
与往常一样，如果您有任何疑问，请在下面的评论中提出。
If you found this video useful, please click like and subscribe.
如果您觉得此视频有用，请单击“赞”并订阅。
I will see you in the next video.
我将在下一个视频中见到你。
Bye for now.
再见。
[BLANK_AUDIO]